So I'm here to explain
أنا هنا لاشرح
why I'm wearing these ninja pajamas.
لماذا أرتدي ملابس النينجا هذه.
And to do that, I'd like to talk first
ولأفعل ذلك، أود أن أتحدث أولا عن
about environmental toxins in our bodies.
سميات البيئة في أجسادنا.
So some of you may know
البعض منكم ربما يعرف
about the chemical Bisphenol A, BPA.
عن ثنائي الفينول الكيميائي أ، بي بي أ (A,BPA).
It's a material hardener and synthetic estrogen
إنه مادة صلبة وإستروجين صناعي
that's found in the lining of canned foods
يوجد في الأطعمة المعلبة
and some plastics.
وبعض المواد البلاستيكية.
So BPA mimics the body's own hormones
أ ب أيه يقلد هرمونات الجسم
and causes neurological and reproductive problems.
ويسبب مشاكل عصبية وتناسلية.
And it's everywhere.
إنه في كل مكان.
A recent study found BPA
أظهرت نتائج دراسة حديثة ال أ ب أيه
in 93 percent of people six and older.
يوجد في 93 بالمائة من الناس منذ سن السادسة فما فوق.
But it's just one chemical.
لكنه عنصر كيميائي واحد.
The Center for Disease Control in the U.S.
مركز مكافحة الأمراض بالولايات المتحدة
says we have 219 toxic pollutants in our bodies,
قال توجد في أجسامنا 219 من السميات الملوثة،
and this includes preservatives, pesticides
وهي تشمل على المواد الحافظة والمبيدات
and heavy metals like lead and mercury.
ومعادن ثقيلة مثل الرصاص والزئبق.
To me, this says three things.
بالنسبة لي، هذا يفسر ثلاثة أشياء.
First, don't become a cannibal.
الأول، لاتصبح آكل لحوم البشر.
Second, we are both responsible for and the victims of
الثاني، جميعنا مسؤولون عن وضحايا
our own pollution.
تلوثنا.
And third,
والثالث،
our bodies are filters and storehouses
أن أجسادنا فلاتر ومخازن
for environmental toxins.
للسموم البيئية.
So what happens to all these toxins when we die?
ما الذي يحدث لجميع هذه السموم عند موتنا.
The short answer is:
الإجابة باختصار هي:
They return to the environment in one way or another,
أنها ترجع إلى البيئة بطريقة أو أخرى،
continuing the cycle of toxicity.
لتستمر الدورة السمية.
But our current funeral practices
لكن ممارستنا الجنائزية الحالية
make the situation much worse.
تجعل الوضع أكثر سوءً.
If you're cremated,
في حالة حرق جثتك،
all those toxins I mentioned are released into the atmosphere.
جميع السموم التي ذكرتها ستتصاعد في الغلاف الجوي.
And this includes 5,000 pounds of mercury
وهذه تتضمن 5,000 رطلا من الزئبق
from our dental fillings alone every year.
من حشوات الأسنان لوحدها كل عام.
And in a traditional American funeral,
ففي تقليد تشيع الجنائز الأمريكية،
a dead body is covered with fillers and cosmetics
يتم تغطية الجثة بحشوات الأسنان ومستحضرات التجميل
to make it look alive.
لتجعل الجسد يبدو على قيد الحياة.
It's then pumped with toxic formaldehyde
وبعدها يتم ضخ الجسد بغاز الفورمالديهايد السام
to slow decomposition --
لإبطاء التحلل --
a practice which causes respiratory problems and cancer
وهي عملية تتسبب في مشاكل في الجهاز التنفسي والسرطان
in funeral personnel.
للعاملين في مجال الدفن.
So by trying to preserve our dead bodies,
ولذا عند محاولات حفظ جثثنا،
we deny death, poison the living
فإننا ننكر الموت، نسمم الحياة
and further harm the environment.
وأكثر من ذلك نلوث البيئة.
Green or natural burials, which don't use embalming,
عمليات الدفن الخضراء أو العادية، التي لايستخدم فيها التحنيط،
are a step in the right direction,
تعتبر خطوة في الاتجاه الصحيح،
but they don't address the existing toxins in our bodies.
لكنها لا تعالج السميات الموجودة في أجسادنا.
I think there's a better solution.
أعتقد بأن هناك حل أفضل.
I'm an artist,
أنا فنانة،
so I'd like to offer a modest proposal
لهذا أود أن أقدم مقترح متواضع
at the intersection
في نقطة تقاطع
of art, science and culture.
الفن، العلوم والثقافة.
The Infinity Burial Project,
مشروع الدفن اللامتناهي،
an alternative burial system
نظام الدفن اللامتناهي
that uses mushrooms
الذي يستخدم الفطر (عش الغراب)
to decompose and clean toxins in bodies.
لتحلل ويزيل السميات من الأجسام.
The Infinity Burial Project
مشروع الدفن اللامتناهي
began a few years ago with a fantasy
بدأ قبل عدة سنوات بتصور
to create the Infinity Mushroom --
لتوفير الفطر (عش الغراب) اللامحدود --
a new hybrid mushroom
فطر (عش الغراب) الهجين الجديد
that would decompose bodies, clean the toxins
الذي ربما يحلل الأجسام، يزيل السموم
and deliver nutrients to plant roots,
ويوفر الغذاء لجذور النبات،
leaving clean compost.
تاركا سمادا نظيفا.
But I learned it's nearly impossible
لكن تعلمت بأنه شبه مستحيل
to create a new hybrid mushroom.
توفير فطر (عش الغراب) هجين جديد.
I also learned
كما تعلمت أيضا
that some of our tastiest mushrooms
بأن بعضا من ألذ فطر (عش الغراب)
can clean environmental toxins in soil.
يمكن أن يزيل السموم البيئية من التربة.
So I thought maybe I could train an army
لذا أعتقد بأنني ربما أتمكن من تدريب قوات
of toxin-cleaning edible mushrooms
من الفطر (عش الغراب) الصالح للأكل المزيل للسموم
to eat my body.
لأكل جسدي.
So today, I'm collecting what I shed or slough off --
الآن، أجمع ما تساقط أو زال من --
my hair, skin and nails --
شعري، جلدي وأظافري --
and I'm feeding these to edible mushrooms.
وأقوم بتغدية الفطر الصالح لأكلها.
As the mushrooms grow,
عندما ينمو الفطر،
I pick the best feeders
ألتقط أفضل المغذيات
to become Infinity Mushrooms.
لتصبح فطر لامتناهي.
It's a kind of imprinting and selective breeding process
إنه نوع البصمة والتكاثر الانتقائي
for the afterlife.
للحياة الآخرى.
So when I die,
وعندما أموت،
the Infinity Mushrooms will recognize my body
سيقوم الفطر اللامتناهي بالتعرف على جسدي
and be able to eat it.
ويتمكن من أكله.
All right, so for some of you,
حسنا، للبعض منكم،
this may be really, really out there.
هذا ربما يكون حقيقة، فعلا في مكان آخر.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
Just a little.
مجرد عنوان.
I realize this is not the kind of relationship
لأقد أدركت هذا بأنه ليس نوعا من العلاقة
that we usually aspire to have with our food.
التي دائما ما نطمح أن تكون مع غذائنا.
We want to eat, not be eaten by, our food.
نريد أن نأكل، ولا نؤكل بواسطة، غذائنا.
But as I watch the mushrooms grow
لكن عند مشاهدتي لنمو الفطر
and digest my body,
وهضم جسدي،
I imagine the Infinity Mushroom
أتصور أن الفطر اللامتناهي
as a symbol of a new way of thinking about death
كنموذج لطريقة جديدة للتفكير في الموت
and the relationship between my body and the environment.
والعلاقة بين جسدي والبيئة.
See for me,
بالنسبة لي،
cultivating the Infinity Mushroom
زراعة الفطر اللامتناهي
is more than just scientific experimentation
هو أكثر من مجرد تجربة علمية
or gardening or raising a pet,
أو زراعة حديقة أو تربية حيوانات أليفة،
it's a step towards accepting the fact
إنها خطوة تجاه قبول حقيقة
that someday I will die and decay.
أنني يوما ما سأموت، وأتعفن.
It's also a step
إنها أيضا خطوة
towards taking responsibility
تجاه تحمل مسئولية
for my own burden on the planet.
أعبائي الخاصة على الكوكب.
Growing a mushroom is also part of a larger practice
نمو الفطرهو أيضا جزء أكبر من ممارسة
of cultivating decomposing organisms
زراعة الكائنات المتحللة
called decompiculture,
التي تسمى اصطلاحا ب الكائنات المتحللة (دي كومبي كلتشر )،
a concept that was developed by an entomologist,
وهو مفهوم قام بتطويره عالم الحشرات،
Timothy Myles.
تيموثي مايلز.
The Infinity Mushroom is a subset of decompiculture
الفطر اللامتناهي هو مجموعة فرعية من مصطلح الكائنات المتحللة (دي كومبي كلتشر )
I'm calling body decompiculture and toxin remediation --
وأطلق على جسد الكئنات المتحللة وعلاج السموم --
the cultivation of organisms that decompose
زراعة الكائنات الحية التي تتحلل
and clean toxins in bodies.
وتزيل السموم من الأجسام.
And now about these ninja pajamas.
والآن عن بجامة النينجا هذه.
Once it's completed,
بمجرد أن تكتمل،
I plan to integrate the Infinity Mushrooms into a number of objects.
لدي خطة لدمج الفطراللامتناهي في عدد من المواضيع.
First, a burial suit
الأول، بدلة دفن
infused with mushroom spores,
مليئة بجراثيم الفطر،
the Mushroom Death Suit.
بدلة الفطر للموت.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
I'm wearing the second prototype
أنا أرتدي النموذج الثاني
of this burial suit.
من بدلة الدفن هذه.
It's covered with a crocheted netting
إنها مغطاه بحياكة الكروشيه
that is embedded with mushroom spores.
وهي تتضمن جراثيم الفطر.
The dendritic pattern you see
النمط الشجيري الذي ترونه
mimics the growth of mushroom mycelia,
يحاكي نمو فطريات الميسيليا
which are the equivalent of plant roots.
التي تعادل جذور النبات.
I'm also making a decompiculture kit,
وأنا أيضا أصنع طقم الكائنات المتحللة،
a cocktail of capsules
مزيج من الكبسولات
that contain Infinity Mushroom spores
التي تحتوي جراثيم الفطر اللامتناهي
and other elements
وعناصر أخرى
that speed decomposition and toxin remediation.
تلك التي تسرع عملية التحلل وعلاج السموم.
These capsules are embedded in a nutrient-rich jelly,
هذه الكبسولات مضمنة في هلام غني بالغذاء،
a kind of second skin,
نوع من الجلد الثاني،
which dissolves quickly
الذي يذوب بسرعة
and becomes baby food for the growing mushrooms.
ويصير طعام مبدئي للفطريات المتنامية.
So I plan to finish the mushroom and decompiculture kit
لذا أخطط لإنهاء الفطر وطقم الكائنات المتحللة
in the next year or two,
خلال العام المقبل أو سنتين،
and then I'd like to begin testing them,
ومن ثم أود البدء في إجراء التجارب عليها،
first with expired meat from the market
أولا بتجربة اللحم من السوق
and then with human subjects.
ومن ثم على البشر.
And believe it or not,
صدق أو لا تصدق،
a few people have offered to donate their bodies to the project
تقدمت مجموعة من الناس للتبرع باجسادها للمشروع
to be eaten by mushrooms.
لتؤكل بالفطر.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
What I've learned from talking to these folks
ما تعلمته من الحديث إلى هؤلاء الناس -المتقدمون-
is that we share a common desire
هو أننا نتقاسم رغبة مشتركة
to understand and accept death
لفهم وقبول الموت
and to minimize the impact of our death on the environment.
وتقليل تأثير موتنا على البيئة.
I wanted to cultivate this perspective
أردت أن أغرس وجهة النظر
just like the mushrooms,
مثل الفطر،
so I formed the Decompiculture Society,
لذا قمت بتشكيل مجتمع الكائنات المتحللة،
a group of people called decompinauts
مجموعة من الناس تدعى (دي كومبناتس)
who actively explore their postmortem options,
الذين يستكشفون خيارات ما بعد وفاتهم،
seek death acceptance
يسعون لقبول الموت
and cultivate decomposing organisms
وزراعة الكائنات المتحللة
like the Infinity Mushroom.
مثل الفطر اللامتناهي.
The Decompiculture Society shares a vision
مجتمع الكائنات المتحللة يتشارك رؤية
of a cultural shift,
تغير الثقافة،
from our current culture of death denial and body preservation
من ثقافتنا الحالية لانكار الموت والمحافظة على الجسد
to one of decompiculture,
إلى ثقافة الكائنات المتحللة،
a radical acceptance of death and decomposition.
قبول جذري للموت والتحلل.
Accepting death means accepting
إن قبول الموت يعني قبول
that we are physical beings
أننا كائنات طبيعية
who are intimately connected to the environment,
تلك التي ترتبط ارتباطا وثيقا بالبيئة،
as the research on environmental toxins confirms.
كما أكد ذلك البحث عن السموم البيئية.
And the saying goes,
ويقول المثل،
we came from dust and will return to dust.
أتينا من التراب وسنرجع إلى التراب
And once we understand that we're connected to the environment,
وبمجرد فهمنا إننا نرتبط بالبيئة،
we see that the survival of our species
نرى بأن بقاء جنسنا
depends on the survival of the planet.
يعتمد على بقاء كوكب الأرض.
I believe this is the beginning
أعتقد بأن هذه هي البداية
of true environmental responsibility.
للمسؤولية البيئية الحقيقية.
Thank you.
شكرا لكم.
(Applause)
(تصفيق)